Hey English learners, welcome to this A1
English listening practice video. I'm
cold right now. I hope you're warmer
than I am, but I'm outside and it's
cold. That's why I have a sweatshirt on.
But I'm happy to talk to you today in
this A1 listening practice video. Today
I'm going to talk about some of my
childhood hobbies, the activities that I
liked to do when I was a kid or a
teenager. So, I'm sure you'll enjoy this
practice video. Remember that if you
want my help to actually understand
people when they speak fast, then make
sure to sign up for my training. You can
get my listening practice seminars by
signing up for my membership. That link
is down below. So, let's talk about some
of my childhood hobbies.
I liked to do many different activities
as a kid. I loved trying new things. Uh
I still do. I love trying different
things and I often changed hobbies. I uh
started one hobby and then I got bored
with it and then I started a different
hobby. So I tried many different
activities as a kid and even as a young
adult I still liked to do this. Try one
thing then try another thing. So uh I
always like trying new things. Even
today I like trying new things. So let
me talk about some of the different
things I liked to do when I was a kid.
Um I really liked collecting things. I
think many of you did this when you were
a child. Uh, I liked collecting
different cards. Like, of course,
Pokemon cards. Many of you probably
collected or maybe you still collect
Pokemon cards. I liked these when I was
a kid. Uh, I also collected Yu-Gi-Oh
cards. And I not only collected Yu-Gi-Oh
cards, I also played the game, the card
game. So, I really liked Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
I also had some Magic cards, Magic the
Gathering, it's called, but I wasn't
super interested in Magic the Gathering.
And I also had some Digimon cards. Some
of you might remember Digimon. Uh it
wasn't as popular as Pokemon or
Yu-Gi-Oh, but I also had some of those
cards. And I also collected other things
besides cards. I actually collected
bugs. I know that sounds a little
strange to many of you, but I liked bugs
when I was a little kid. I loved finding
different bugs and putting them in a
container, like something that I could
put them in and close. And I would put
different bugs in the same container and
I would watch them uh interact like what
they would do with each other and I
would study them and [clears throat]
I uh would feed them. I fed them fruit
or different things like that. Uh like I
remember having caterpillars
and feeding them I think cantaloupe and
other fruit. Uh so I liked bugs when I
was a kid. I also liked collecting
animal bones. This sounds weird, I know,
but where I grew up, there were a lot of
hills uh around the house where I lived.
And there were different animals like
snakes and rabbits and squirrels and
birds and different animals.
And uh sometimes I would play in the the
hills and uh I would find animal bones
on the ground and I was a little boy and
I thought this was cool. So, I collected
these animal bones and I had a snake
skeleton
and the head of like a mouse or a
squirrel maybe. I can't remember, but I
had different animal bones. So, now I
find that kind of [laughter]
gross. But when I was a young kid, it
was fun. I was a curious boy. Okay. I
also liked making paper airplanes.
Uh where you fold the paper and create
an airplane and you can throw these uh
paper airplanes and they fly. I actually
just made a paper airplane for my son
yesterday. So, I still like this. Uh but
when I was a kid, I loved making paper
airplanes and trying to uh throw them
high in the sky and hopefully they would
fly for a long time before hitting the
ground. Uh so uh that was really fun. I
I loved inventing new paper airplanes.
Uh I tried to find the best way to make
the airplane to uh make it stay in the
sky for longer. So that was really fun
uh when I was a kid and it's still fun
now. Uh, I also played airsoft, uh,
where you shoot these little BB's, we
call them. Uh, they hurt when they hit
you, but, uh, you can, uh, shoot these
at each other. And uh I would play with
my friends outside with uh these airsoft
guns and we would hide behind trees and
it was fun. [laughter]
Of course, uh a lot of young boys or
teenagers like shooting these fake guns,
these airsoft guns. Uh it's a fun
activity. I also liked video games like
most boys. Uh most boys like video games
I think. Uh I had Super Nintendo.
That was my first video game uh console
and N64.
I also had an Xbox, a PlayStation,
and I also played some computer games,
too. Uh I wasn't
uh super
uh fan of video games. I just liked them
like most kids, but I didn't play for
many, many hours. I know other people
who loved video games more than me and
they played for many hours. Some of them
still play for many hours. I wasn't like
that. Uh I liked video games, but I
liked doing other things, too. Uh, I
didn't just spend all day playing video
games. Uh, and another thing that I
really liked and I still really like is
reading. I loved reading when I was a
kid. In fact, uh, my mother would take
me to the library
all the time to check out books. meaning
you rent the book and then you have to
give it back to the library when you're
done. So my mom would take me to check
out library books and I had so much fun
choosing the different books that I
wanted to read. Uh, I really liked
reading as a kid and that's probably why
I still really like reading. Uh, the
people who I know now who don't like to
read, they didn't like to read when they
were kids either. So I think that when
you have this hobby, this activity,
you like reading when you're a kid.
Usually you like reading when you're an
adult. So I hope that my kids like to
read. I uh buy them books. They have a
lot of books. So hopefully they will
enjoy reading like I did when I was a
kid and then they'll probably like
reading when they're adults too. So
reading was another hobby of mine. And I
also played many sports. Many sports. I
played basketball, tennis, football,
baseball, soccer,
many sports. I played them at different
times in my childhood. I played soccer
when I was really young, but then I
stopped playing. Uh I played uh tennis
when I was really young too, but I also
stopped playing tennis. I played
basketball
for for longer, for more time. So I
played basketball even when I was a
teenager. And so some sports I played uh
for longer, some sports I played for
only a couple years, like baseball. I
think I only played baseball for a
couple years. But I also really liked
the interesting
uh sports that aren't the normal sports
that we watch on TV. Like for example, I
really liked bowling. And you can watch
bowling on TV, but it's not as popular
as the bigger sports like basketball,
soccer, tennis, etc. I loved bowling. I
loved pingpong. Uh like table tennis. I
loved pingpong. And I really really
liked pool or billiards where you use
the stick to hit the balls into the
pockets. I really liked playing pool and
I uh played all of those sports pretty
often uh during some uh periods of my
life. Like when I was uh in high school
or I think middle school. When I was in
middle school, I uh really liked bowling
and I went bowling all the time. I also
really liked fishing when I was in
middle school and uh during one summer I
went fishing like every week or twice a
week. I really liked fishing. So, I
loved all of those different types of
sports, the major sports like
basketball, football, baseball,
etc. And also the other sports like
pingpong and pool and bowling like those
sports as well. All right, hopefully you
enjoyed this video. I know it was good
practice for your listening. Remember
that if you want my help to understand
native English speakers when they speak
fast, then join my membership so you can
get my training which will help you do
that. So the link is down below. All
right. Thank you all for watching this
video and I'll talk to you in the next